妮妮
Hey, Bernie.
我的性感小太空人还好吗
Hey, how's my little astronautie hottie?
还行吧
Okay, I guess.
只是被困在这...
It's just, being cooped up in this...
"锡盒"里有段时日  快受不了
tin can for weeks on end is starting to get to me.
坚持下去啊  再多撑几天
Well, hang in there. You just have a couple more days to go,
-就能回家了  -我知道
- and then you'll be home. - I know.
我要继续工作了
I got to get back to work.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - Love you too.
妮妮
Hey, Bernie?
你走之前可以帮我做件事吗
Before you go, can you do something for me?
你想我做什么呢
What do you want me to do?
是这样的
Okay, here it is.
我好想念地心引力
I really miss gravity.
你可以让我看看东西垂直落下的样子吗
Can you drop something so I can watch it fall?
真的吗  你真想看啊
Really, you're serious?
好吧
Okay.
哎哟  宝贝  我要爽死了
Oh, baby, you're killing me.
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon?
今天来了一个你的包裹  你妈寄的
This came for you today. It's from your mom.
谢谢你  佩妮
Thank you, Penny.
稍等...  给
Yeah, wait... here.
你的辛苦费
For your troubles.
妈呀  整整一元大洋呢
Oh, boy, a whole dollar.
我可以不用去送报了
Now, I can quit my paper route.
-里面是什么啊  -根本无所谓
- So, what's in it? - Mmm, doesn't matter.
通常他都是隔着盒子玩[模型玩具]而已
Half the time, he just ends up playing with the box.
是我小时候写的日志与研究报告啦
Yeah, it's journals and research papers I wrote as a child.
真有爱
Aw, how cute.
这就跟日记一样吗
Is this like a diary?
不是  那是我的如厕训练日志
No, that's my potty training journal.
-不是吧  你的如厕训练日志啊  -是的
- Really, your potty training journal? - Yeah.
字迹难看  多多包涵
And forgive my crude penmanship.
我六岁之后才开始打字
I didn't start typing until I was six.
"8月7号  上午8点42分
"August 7, 8:42 A.M.
这真是太丢人了  这尿布是怎么回事"
This is humiliating. What was wrong with diapers?"
后面还有图表
There are some charts in the back
记录我的屎形  屎色与软硬度
where I kept track of shape, color and consistency.
真恶心
Disgusting.
真正恶心的是他到现在都还会做记录
No, what's disgusting is he's still keeping track.
-你为什么要这些玩意啊  -别别别
- Why do you need all this stuff...? - No, no, no, no...
-抱歉  -问得好
- Sorry! - I am glad you asked.
你知道希格斯玻色子吗
Yeah, are you familiar with the Higgs boson?
希格斯玻色子:  又称为上帝粒子]
当然知道啊  新闻上都有
Of course, it is... it's been in the news.
超出名的玻色子
And it's a very famous boson.
你少来了
Nice try.
在1964年时  彼得·希格斯博士
Now, in 1964, Dr. Peter Higgs,
一个成功自信的物理学家
accomplished self-promoter and physicist,
写了文章假定一种亚原子粒子
he wrote a paper postulating the existence
"希格斯玻色子"的存在
of a subatomic particle called the Higgs boson.
当年  这文章被人给驳回了
Now, initially, the paper was rejected,
知道最近  才验证出  其实他是对的
but recently, he was proven right.
现在他要得诺贝尔奖  简直探囊取物
And now he's on the fast track to win a Nobel prize.
这不就是我刚说的吗
Yeah, that's basically what I said.
重点是
The point is
希格斯正被人赞赏着他50年前的发现
Higgs is being celebrated for work he did 50 years ago,
这让我不禁思考
so that got me thinking,
说不定我早想到了值得得奖的东西
perhaps I've already hit upon the idea
而它们就藏在这些日志里
that will win me my Nobel prize.
原来他们会颁发奖项给
I didn't know they gave Nobel prizes
拉粑粑进小马桶呀
for making boom-boom in the potty.
你真的觉得里面能找出什么科学发现吗
You really think there's some kind of scientific discovery in here?
这箱子里只有我上幼儿园前的作品
Well, this box only covers my work through nursery school.
后面还有很多呢
There's a good deal more to come.
我真正在学术理论上取得进步
I didn't really hit my academic stride
是在我取消了浪费时间的"户外游玩"之后
until I cut out that time-suck known as "playing outdoors."
你打算花费大把时间
So, you're going to spend hours and hours
重读这些玩意啊
combing through all this stuff?
这话说得对
That's a good point.
我的时间太宝贵了
My time is much too valuable.
或许我该找个人帮我干这事
You know, perhaps I should find someone to do it for me.
找个有着基本科学知识
You know, someone with a rudimentary understanding of science,
但在苦力活上更有天分的人
but whose real talents lie in menial labor.
想都别想
Not gonna happen.
我要不是觉得你能行
Yeah, well, if I didn't think you could handle it,
我才不会问你呢
I wouldn't be asking.
真要人帮忙  你还是去找个研究生吧
If you want help, just hire a grad student.
我说不定能帮上忙啊
Maybe I could do it.
就你  真的吗
You, really?
你会懂得评估我作品的好坏吗
You can assess the quality of my work?
好吧  给
Okay, um, here.
这是我五岁时写的
I wrote this when I was five years old.
"证明代数拓扑永远不会有
"A proof that algebraic topology can never have
不会自我冲突的交换群"
a non-self contradictory set of abelian groups."
在你眼里  我就是一金发猴子是吧
I'm just a blonde monkey to you, aren't I?
这可是自己说  我什么都没说
You said it, not me.
生活大爆炸 第六季第三集
好的  詹森女士
All right, Ms. Jenson.
开始之前  需要来点东西提神吗
Uh, before we begin, may I offer you a refreshment?
水  咖啡  茶
Water, coffee, tea,
或来根大麻烟吗
a marijuana cigarette?
不用了  谢谢  不需要
No, thanks. I'm fine.
不用客气哦
Now, are you sure?
这玩意大家都抽
Everyone's smoking them.
我觉得这玩意爽爆了
I think they're the best.
我不碰毒
I don't do drugs.
太棒了
Excellent, yeah.
刚是陷阱题
That was a ruse.
那玩意才不爽
They're not the best.
物理才是最爽的
Physics is the best.
随便说句  选咖啡也是不行的哦
And by the way, coffee was also an unacceptable choice.
好了  资料上写着你来自爱荷华州的得梅因
All right, so I see here you're from Des Moines, Iowa.
你的理论物理学以最优异的成绩
Uh, you're summa cum laude in theoretical physics
毕业于斯坦福大学
from Stanford University.
两年前  你耳朵受持续性感染所苦
Oh, and two years ago, you had a persistent ear infection.
希望那没影响你的听力
I hope that didn't cause any hearing loss.
没有  当然没有
No, of course not.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know about that?
我对你的背景做了全面的调查
I did a comprehensive background check.
医疗记录  信用记录  犯罪史等等
Medical records, credit reports, criminal history.
我相信你已经缴清了那些停车罚单了吧
I trust you paid off those parking tickets.
是的  我付清了
Yes, I did.
很好  听力没问题
Hearing unimpaired, good.
库珀博士  我真的很希望能得到这个机会
Look, Dr. Cooper, I really want this position.
能为您这样才华洋溢的人做事
It would be an incredible honor to work for
真是我天大的荣幸
a man of your brilliance.
溜须拍马是没用的  詹森女士
Flattery will not get you this job, Ms. Jenson.
陈述的是事实  又何来逢迎拍马
It's not flattery if it's the truth.
谢谢  欢迎加入
Well, thank you. Welcome aboard.
你最近有跟霍华德通话吗
You talk to Howard lately?
有啊  就昨晚
Uh, yeah, last night.
他一直让我把铅笔从空中落下给他看
He kept making me drop pencils for him.
感觉好不舒服哦
I got uncomfortable.
谢尔顿  但愿你饿了
Hey, Sheldon, hope you're hungry.
今天中饭有通心粉和...
They're serving macaroni and...
芝士哟
cheese.
厉害
Smooth.
-你好  -你们好
- Hi. - Hello.
谢尔顿  你不介绍一下吗
Sheldon, aren't you going to introduce us?
不必  有人会为我代劳
No. I have people for that now.
你来
You're up.
我是艾利克斯  库珀博士的新助手
I'm Alex, Dr. Cooper's new assistant.
恭喜你  同时也愿上帝怜悯你的灵魂
Ah, congratulations and may God have mercy on your soul.
我是莱纳德  这位是拉杰
I'm Leonard. This is Raj.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
能与库珀博士共事  我非常兴...
I'm so excited to be working with Dr...
詹森女士  闲聊请留到休息时间
Yeah, please reserve chitchat for your breaks, Ms. Jenson.
对了  我们没有休息时间
Yeah, FYI, there will be no breaks.
我得继续工作了
I should probably get to work.
她看起来不错
She seems nice.
喂  你都有女朋友了
Hey, you already got a girlfriend.
所以这妞归我
I call dibs.
我就说了一句"她看起来不错"
All I said was, "she seems nice."
是啊  可我爱上她了
Yeah, well, I love her.
没想到今天你会打给我
Hey, I wasn't expecting to hear from you today.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
不  不是很好
Uh, no, not really.
怎么了
What's wrong?
还记得联盟号宇宙飞船吗
Well, remember the... Soyuz capsule
那个要来接我们回地球的玩意
they were sending to bring us home?
被推迟了
It's delayed.
我们至少还要再这里呆上一周
We're gonna be here at least another week.
或许10天左右
Maybe ten days.
俄罗斯人说的  我也不敢信
It's the Russians, so you don't know.
1957年 俄罗斯把一只狗  "莱卡"给送上太空
五个小时后因宇宙飞行服隔热不佳成为"火烧狗"
目前它的尸体与当年的太空舱还滞留在地球轨道上
他们送上来的狗  尸体都没回去呢
They left dogs up here in the '60s.
拜托  霍华德
Come on, Howard.
没人会把你留那里不管的
No one's leaving you up there.
我不知道我还能坚持多久
I don't know how much longer I can take this.
我睡不着
I can't sleep,
零重力让我胃酸倒流得厉害
and zero gravity is giving me crazy acid reflux.
我的抗酸补钙果味咀嚼片就剩最后3片了
I'm down to my last three Tums.
你会没事的
You're going to be fine.
你跟你妈参加减肥训练营  你都生存下来了
You survived that Weight Watchers cruise with your mom.
令人开心的冰激凌不也是第二天就没了吗
And they ran out of low-fat ice cream on day two.
你先冷静下来  深呼吸几口气
Just calm down and take a few deep breaths.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
我这是干嘛  把氧气都耗光了
What am I doing? I'm using up all the oxygen.
如果我死了  你要保证会为我守身如玉
If I die, promise you'll never have sex with another man.
很好
Oh, yeah.
我现在是个食男妇了
I'm a man-eater now.
好了  最后一步  用这个睫毛夹
Okay, for the final touch, this is an eyelash curler.
放在你睫毛上  然后贴近眼皮轻轻夹
You just place it on your lashes and squeeze it closed.
不知道呢
Oh, I don't know.
迪士尼动画片《小飞侠》中
小飞侠彼得潘的精灵小伙伴
看起来像仙女小叮当的妇科医生的工具
Looks like something used by Tinker Bell's gynecologist.
虎克船长出自迪士尼动画片《小飞侠》
有着铁钩手的凶恶坏人
但愿她的妇科医生不是虎克船长
Who I hope for her sake is not Captain Hook, so...
你打给谁
Who are you calling?
我要跟谢尔顿视频聊天
I'm going to video-chat Sheldon.
如果我的新形象激发起他的性欲
If my new look leads to phone sex,
那你只好暂时离开房间一下咯
I'm going to have to ask you to leave the room.
库珀博士办公室
Dr. Cooper's office.
你好  请问您是哪位
Oh, hello. Who are you?
我是艾利克斯  库珀博士的助手
I'm Alex, Dr. Cooper's assistant.
有什么可以帮您的吗
Can I help you?
我要找谢尔顿
I'd like to speak to Sheldon.
抱歉  他让我过滤所有电话
I'm sorry. He's asked me to hold all calls
除非打来的人是斯蒂芬·霍金  他妈妈
unless you're Stephen Hawking, his mother
或是来自未来的他自己
or himself from the future.
好吧
All right.
-告诉他艾米找他  -请问您贵姓
- Well, tell him Amy called. - Last name?
他知道我姓什么
He knows my last name.
我可是他的女朋友
I'm his girlfriend.
我们恋爱合同资料全有
We have a contract and everything.
我会发你份文件  以兹证明
I'll send you a PDF.
好的  我会转告他
All right, I will tell him you called.
-好奇怪啊  -怎么了
- Hmm, that's weird.  - What?
谢尔顿告诉我他新的助理叫艾利克斯
Sheldon told me he had a new assistant named Alex.
却没说是个女艾利克斯
He didn't mention that Alex was a girl.
也许是他没发现人家是女的呢
Maybe he didn't notice.
有道理
You're right.
我完全不必担心谢尔顿
I don't have to worry about Sheldon.
确实
No, you do not.
我该担心的是那个女的
It's her I have to worry about.
艾米你不是吧
Oh, Amy, really?
-她会爱上谢尔顿的  -怎么可能
- She is not going to come on to Sheldon.  - Oh, really?
看看这萌脸
Look at this face.
一个女人每天与这萌脸共处八小时
How can any woman spend eight hours a day
怎么可能不爱上他呢
alone with this face and not fall in love with it?
首先我要说
Well, for starters,
那脸一开始讲话  就什么都幻灭了
at some point, that face starts talking.
艾米  这太夸张了
Amy, this is crazy.
你根本不用怀疑什么
You have nothing to be suspicious about.
我不是怀疑
I'm not suspicious.
我只是路过  跟我男朋友打个招呼
I just want to stop in, say hi to my boyfriend
然后见见新助理
and meet his new assistant.
-可以走了吗  -稍等
- Can we go now?  - Hang on.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
这还不明显吗
Isn't it obvious?
我在用体味申明领地
I'm spreading my scent to mark my territory.
-得了吧  没用的  -真的吗
- Come on, Amy. That is not gonna work.  - Really?
在你成为我闺蜜之前
Because just before you became my best friend,
我也对你整间公寓做了同样的事
I did this all over your apartment.
你的助理  有提到过我吗
Has your, uh, assistant said anything about me?
其实还真有
In fact, she has.
她的原话是  "这家伙什么毛病"
Uh, her exact words were, "What is that guy's problem?"
她记住我了  好戏开始
I'm in her head. Let the dance begin.
你的冷冻优格  库珀博士
Here's your frozen yogurt, Dr. Cooper.
这该有意思了
This should be fun.
一半巧克力  一半香草
Half chocolate, half vanilla,
-挨着的  没搅在一起吗  -对
- side by side, not swirled? - Yes.
-半茶匙碎末  -彩虹的 不是巧克力的
Half a teaspoon of sprinkles? Rainbow, not chocolate.
-两颗樱桃  -一颗在上  一颗在下
- Two cherries?  - One on top, one on the bottom.
-茎拿掉么了  -呃
- Stems removed?  - Um...
上边的拿掉了
top one, yes.
下面的我没检查
I didn't check the one on the bottom.
不好意思  库珀博士
I'm so sorry, Dr. Cooper.
没事的  艾利克斯
It's all right, Alex.
我并不生气  只是很失望
I'm not mad at you; I'm just disappointed.
等等  艾利克斯  要跟我们一起吃吗
Wait, Alex. Do you want to join us?
艾利克斯  稍等片刻
Uh, Alex, a moment.
我有些话要跟霍夫斯塔德博士说
I need a word with Dr. Hofstadter.
你觉得她跟我们一起坐合适吗
Do you think it's appropriate for her to sit with us,
就凭她的身份
given her station?
凭她的什么
Given her what?
要说我从PBS台的英剧里学到什么的话
If I've learned anything from British television shows on PBS,
那就是仆人和他的同伴们都是坐楼下吃饭的
it's that servants dine downstairs with their own kind.
什么
What?
这是种仁慈  莱纳德
It's a kindness, Leonard.
不然的话你就是在残酷地引诱他们
Otherwise, you're cruelly tempting them with a glimpse
体验一下比满手油烟更高层次的生活
of a world that's just beyond their soot-stained fingertips.
那必须
Oh, sure.
请坐吧
Please join us.
好的  谢谢
Oh, okay. Thank you.
艾利克斯  你毕业论文的题目是什么
So, Alex, what's the topic of your dissertation?
在地球的L5拉格朗日点
I'm looking for Trojan asteroids
寻找特洛伊小行星
at Earth's L-Five Lagrange point.
这正巧是
Oh, that happens to be
库萨帕里博士的专业领域呢
Dr. Koothrappali's field of expertise.
你们有很多东西可以聊
You two have a lot to talk about.
真的吗
Is that true?
他还好吗
Is he all right?
不
No.
但跟你的老板相比
But compared to your boss,
他就是精神正常的代表
he's the poster boy for sanity.
还好啦  我这辈子都在和科学家打交道
It's okay, I've been around scientists all my life.
我爸是SETI的天文学家
My dad's an astronomer at SETI.
SETI  寻找外太空星球智慧生命计划
Oh, SETI-- the Search for Extraterrestrial Intelligence.
把谢尔顿介绍给你爸  他就不用搜寻了
You should introduce him to Sheldon. The search is over.
那你是做什么研究的
So, what kind of research are you doing?
-高能激光  -军用吗
- High-energy lasers.  - Ooh. Military?
还没呢  但我能从两英里外替人激光除毛
Not yet, but I can remove unwanted hair from two miles away.
你是对的
You were right.
我没什么可担心的
I had nothing to worry about.
这骚货是你的问题  不是我的
That skank's your problem, not mine.
-你真幽默  霍夫斯塔德博士  -谢谢
- You're very funny, Dr. Hofstadter.  - Thank you.
啊  樱茎  樱茎
Aah! Cherry stem! Cherry stem!
华仔你还好吗  感觉好点了吗
How you doing, Howie? You feeling a little better?
好多了  谢谢  等一下
Oh, a lot better, thanks. One sec.
听好了  我时间不多
Listen close. I don't have a lot of time.
我要你赶紧去我家
I need you to go to my house.
在我房间里有个火箭模型
In my bedroom, you'll find a model rocket.
我要你把它带回你家
I want you to take it and bring it back to your place.
好的
Okay...
第二步  照着建一个14层楼高的版本
Step 2: build a version roughly 14 stories high.
装满火箭燃油来接我
Fill it full of rocket fuel and come get me.
我会给你把门留着的
I'll leave the door unlocked.
华仔  亲爱的  也许你该跟别人谈谈
Howie, honey, maybe you should talk to someone,
让他们知道你有些焦虑
let them know you're having a little anxiety.
不  不  我很好
No, no, I'm fine.
没有焦虑症
No anxiety!
咱们还是用暗号交流吧
We should probably talk in code.
从现在起  小蛙是我  三明治是你
From now on, "Frog" is me, "Sandwich" means you
柠檬是火箭  快点  三明治
and "Lemon" means rocket. So, come on, sandwich,
给我造架柠檬  小蛙要回家
build me a lemon 'cause froggy wants to come home!
瞧你  还假装坚强
Look at you, putting on a brave face.
没什么好需要坚强的
There's nothing to be brave about.
-我没事  -真的吗
- Everything's fine. - Really?
我不知道你对灵长类动物行为知道多少
I don't know how much you know about primate behavior,
不过谢尔顿的助理绝对在向莱纳德求欢
but Sheldon's assistant was clearly courting Leonard.
如果她是狒狒  肯定会弯下身
Were she a mandrill, she would have bent over
展示她那看似大红色蹭鞋垫的
and displayed her brightly colored hindquarters
鲜亮斑斓后臀
like a big red welcome mat.
顺便说下  如果在低年级毕业舞会上试这招
By the way, you try that at the junior prom,
会被踢出去的
you get kicked out.
好吧  也许她是在和他调情  可谁在乎啊
Okay, maybe she was flirting with him, but who cares?
我都不知道我现在和莱纳德的关系算什么
Look, I don't even know where my relationship is with Leonard is right now.
这是你的前额叶在说话
So says your prefrontal cortex.
但同时  你大脑中的边缘系统在计算
But meanwhile, the limbic system of your brain is calculating
如果有另一个女人对莱纳德有兴趣
that if another woman is attracted to Leonard,
那肯定是因为他值得拥有
it must be because he's desirable.
他当然值得拥有了
Well, of course he's desirable.
他棒极了
I mean, he's great.
他聪明  温柔
He's smart, he's sweet,
而且在房事上  老天
and, ooh, in the bedroom, whew,
我告诉你  他真是拼了老命了
let me tell you, he really tries.
所以这事让你烦心
So it doesbother you.
好吧  是让我有点烦
Fine, it bothers me a little.
算了  这太傻了
No. You know what? This is stupid.
我才不烦呢
It doesn't bother me.
好吧  我很烦
Okay, it bothers me.
但只是因为她很捧场他的笑话
But only because she wouldn't stop laughing.
莱纳德没那么幽默搞笑
Leonard is not that funny.
这就是了
And there you have it;
前额叶理性对抗边缘系统的欲望
prefrontal cortex reasoning versus limbic lust.
如果这是拳击赛  就会叫做
If this were a boxing match, they might call it
"马尼拉的震颤"是拳王阿里的著名冠军争夺战
"扁桃体的震颤"
"The thrilla adjacent to the amygdala."
如果你是脑部学家
If you were a brain scientist,
你现在肯定会笑到尿裤子
you would be busting a gut right now!
今天工作怎么样
So, how was work today?
还行吧
Ah, it was all right, I guess.
用海氏急救法拯救樱桃梗卡气管的谢尔顿
Got to Heimlich a cherry stem out of Sheldon.
结果那梗还喷到拉杰的眼睛
Caught Raj right in the eye.
真的假的
You're kidding.
拉杰都得去医疗室了
No, Raj had to go to the nurse.
还有什么事吗
Wow. Anything else?
护士是个女的  所以他没法开口说话
Mmm, the nurse is a woman, so he couldn't talk to her.
她不得不给他拿个芝麻街里的公仔
She had to bring him a Grover puppet
让他指出他哪里疼
so he could point at what hurt.
就这些吗
Is that it?
这还不够精彩吗
Isn't that enough?
有武器化的水果与公仔
It had the weaponized fruit and a puppet.
你还想听什么刺激的
What more do you want?
太好了  莱纳德  你在家
Oh, good, Leonard, you're here.
科学新闻
Science news.
你会有兴趣的
This will interest you.
佩妮  想涂指甲请随意
And, Penny, feel free to paint your nails.
有什么新鲜事
What do you got?
我相信艾利克斯发现了
I believe Alex may have unearthed
我的小学科研项目
the grade school science project
也许就是我赢得诺贝尔大奖的机会
that could be my ticket to the Nobel Prize.
请看
Behold.
磁铁  它们吸的是什么
"Magnet What Do They Stick To?"
如果答案是金属  那可能不够开创性
If the answer is "Metal," It's not exactly groundbreaking.
原来的名字是  "再推导
The original title was "A Rederivation
马克斯韦尔的电磁学方程式"
of Maxwell's Equations Regarding Electromagnetism."
我弃用了那个名字
I dumbed it down
因为当时我家乡有些信教的人
because some of the more religious people in town
开始说我是个巫婆
were starting to say I was a witch.
谢尔顿认为这篇论文里的算法可能会改变
Sheldon thinks the approach in this paper might change the way
我们计算磁滞的方法
we calculate ferromagnetic hysteresis.
也是时候了  我讨厌以前的算法
Oh, it's about time. I hated the old way.
-你好  我是佩妮  -我叫艾利克斯
- Hi. I'm Penny. - Alex.
你与霍夫斯塔德博士共事吗
Uh, do you work with Dr. Hofstadter?
在某些方面
In a way.
我们之间有五年长的一系列实验关系
We've kind of been involved in a five-year experiment.
你真幸运  他非常有才华
Oh. Well, you're lucky. He seems very talented.
我肯定很多人想与他共事
And I'm sure a lot of people want to work with him.
很多人没份儿
Well, a lot of people can't.
来吧
Come on.
去哪里
Where are we going?
我的边缘系统想脱掉你的裤子
My limbic system wants to take your pants off.
她人挺好的
She seems nice.
用你自己的时间观察他人  我们正工作呢
Notice people on your own time. We're working.
华仔  感觉还好吗
Hey, Howie, how you feeling?
好些了  好多了
Better. Much better.
其他的宇航员按住我
The other astronauts held me down,
给我来了一针
gave me a shot.
注意  地球人
Attention, people of Earth:
今晚  夜空上会有两个月亮
Tonight, there will be two moons in the sky.
华仔  别这样
Howie, stop that.
太空署看着呢
NASA's watching this!
把裤子穿上
Put your pants back on!